question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The main character in the Half-Life franchise is named Morgan Freeman.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The song Megalovania by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG Undertale.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "DragonForce's 'Through the Fire and Flames' is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Super Mario Bros. was released in 1990.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Undertale is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language Simlish was The Sims (2000).", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Faust is a playable character in Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials and Tribulations as its final game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The game Battlefield 1 takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Half-Life 2 runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Super Mario Bros., the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Sonic Adventure, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of Doomhammer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Team Fortress 2, the Bill's Hat is a reference to the game Dota 2.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game's plot.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG Undertale is a monster.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the game Subnautica, a Cave Crawler will attack you.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The names of Roxas's Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are Oathkeeper and Oblivion.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Starbound, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named Atlas.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Call Of Duty: World At War, the first appearance of the PPSH-41 in Zombies was in the map Der Riese.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In League of Legends, there exists four different types of Dragon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Hidden in the files for Mario Kart Arcade GP is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Sonic the Hedgehog 2 originally was going to have a time travel system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level Hidden Palace Zone was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In career mode of Need for Speed: Underground 2, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The video game Fuel has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The game Garry's Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Paradox Interactive game Stellaris was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Resident Evil, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
